<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Compositable Loadouts</name>
	<author>Wiri</author>
	<packageId>Wiri.compositableloadouts</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Mix and match multiple 'tags' on a single pawn, allowing for composition of loadouts.

&lt;size=24&gt;Features:&lt;/size&gt;
- Create tags containing items which a pawn will wear / pick up / equip automatically
- Create loadouts consisting of multiple tags for flexibility (composition)
- Create bills which make `x` number of items, where `x` is the number of pawns with the tag `y`
- Automatically create bills in a given workbench for all created tags
- Share tags across multiple saves

&lt;size=24&gt;Mod Integrations:&lt;/size&gt;
- Better Workbench Management: When copying a bill which targets a tag to another bill, copy the tag with it.
- Pick up and Haul: Disable pick up patch from our side when PUAH is loaded (duplicate functionality).
- Better Pawn Control: Panic mode integrates with the panic mode in BPC

&lt;size=24&gt;Incompatibilies:&lt;/size&gt;
- Awesome Inventory: Both mods work in the same space, and will never be compatible. Sorry.
- Combat Extended: This mod will be integrated into Combat Extended replacing their existing loadout system in the near (ish) future

&lt;size=24&gt;Credits:&lt;/size&gt;
- DrowsyCorgi ( NotooShabby ) for their incredible work on Awesome Inventory. I hope that it is visible the influence their mod has had; with regards to both the functionality of the mod, and the aesthetics of the GUI.  
- Madman666 for their work creating the custom textures which this mod uses
- All those who helped test, and gave feedback - it all helps
	</description> 
	<url>https://github.com/simplyWiri/Loadout-Compositing</url>

	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>

	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>

	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>NotooShabby.AwesomeInventoryForked</li>		
	</incompatibleWith>

</ModMetaData>